Angie, where are you?
Sylvia, answer me!
(five months later)
The client is chasing me for the revision.
What revisions?
Go change! I'll figure out how to respond.
I want to stay and watch the stars tonight.
When is the sunset?
6:30 p.m., we must wait.
You're right. Can't rush it.
Whatever should happen will happen.
(Mom)
What will you be home today?
You went camping for a few days
and didn't even text me.
I'm worried about you.
You were never this irresponsible.
What is it?
You can see the Venus Conjunction tonight.
What does it mean?
It's a bad omen.
In ancient China, it's called
Taibai entering the Moon,
it usually means war.
That's dangerous. We should take shelter.
Let's go home.
No need. In the western world,
Venus and the Moon are related to love.
It's a romantic celestial phenomenon.
You're just saying that to make me stay.
I'm saying I want to stay and watch,
but you're free to go.
But I want to watch with you
what war and romance are about.
Mom, I'm not coming home tonight.
Your son is fine, don't worry.
What's special about the Venus Conjunction
is the location where they'll meet.
Tell me, mighty one...
what's the meaning of the Venus Conjunction
for a Scorpion?
In astrology,
the Moon affects how people handle
their feelings.
Venus is a symbol of love.
Scorpio seeks the ultimate romance in love.
The Venus Conjunction should mean
unforgettable love.
Unforgettable love?
Should we pledge our undying love?
I remember you're not big on promises.
That's why I didn't promise
not to make a promise.
Unforgettable doesn't mean a pledge
of undying love.
Like a moth to a flame,
that's the ultimate romance.
Knowing it will burn to death,
it's still swarm towards it.
Looks like you figured it out.
The Venus Conjunction?
The owner doesn't want paintings
or decorations on the wall.
But the wife doesn't want to leave it empty.
Now I put in a lamp
with the effect of a halo of
the Venus Conjunction.
They can also change the color
depending on the mood.
See? Your inspiration is always nearby.
But the pace in Hong Kong is too fast.
We only see what's in front of us
and overlook what's around us.
I did not.
My Muse is right next to me.
I'll wash these.
Then I'm off to a client meeting.
My Mom's birthday is coming up.
We'll have dinner with her and
you can meet her.
We'll see.
I take that as a yes.
(Mom)
Auntie?
You must be Sylvia!
Why did you answer the phone?
Where's my son?
Is it something urgent?
He didn't come home because of you?
We stayed one more night to watch the stars.
He should have told me.
He's getting irresponsible as he gets older.
Auntie, you said so he's a grown man.
Don't worry. I'll tell him to call you.
Hello? She cut me off!?
Who is she? She's so rude.
Are you done?
You're checking my phone?
No, your Mom is tracking you down.
Mom? What does she want?
She said you didn't tell her you
won't be home.
You better call her back.
What? I already told her.
Oops, the message didn't go out.
I'm home!
Mom? Mom?
"No need to find me."
Two bamboos.
Pong!
Here he is.
Auntie Ching.
Auntie Bing! Auntie Fung!
What a great hand...Mom!
I told you not to look for me.
But I missed you. Since you weren't home,
I called Auntie Ching to see if you're here.
I know playing mahjong can be tiring,
I brought you Shanghai dishes as a treat.
I'll heat them up for you.
Don't mess up the kitchen.
You have such a sweet tongue,
but you tend to disappear once you go out.
Lan is worried about you.
It was my fault.
I actually sent a message telling you
I won't be home.
But the reception was poor where I was
and I didn't check to make sure it was sent.
It was bad of me to make her worry.
Lan, don't be mad anymore.
What's wrong with you?
He brings food and you change your tune?
Enjoy your game.
I'll heat this up for you.
Have some tea, Mom.
OK, you're forgiven since you coaxed me.
But I seriously doubt your taste.
Your girlfriend was rude and hung up on me.
She's just very straightforward.
She's not a bad person.
She knows about feng shui and divination.
You two should hit it off.
You better give me her name and birthday.
I want to see if you two are compatible.
Siu Zi-yiu, November 11, 1998.
Just the date? What time?
I'll ask.
Your girlfriend must be a witch.
She used black magic to get a hold on you.
No, you have a hold on my heart.
I treat you very well.
I booked a table for your birthday.
I invited Sylvia to celebrate with you.
You'll love her when you meet her.
Try not to be so subjective, OK?
I will get her birth data myself.
OK, whatever you want.
I, Man Nga-kei, born March 15, 1996,
do solemnly ask for a good marriage...
Hey!
Aren't you praying for yourself?
I did that last month.
Since you're here with me
and won't take the initiative,
I'll have to do it on your behalf.
Where else can you find a bestie like me?
May the Lover's Rock help Man Nga-kei
find a good catch,
someone handsome, funny and rich.
But most, most, most importantly,
someone who loves her only.
You must kowtow too. Come on!
1...2...3...
You must touch it.
Throw the wishing placard too.
Wishing placard?
Yes! In one take.
What did you wish for? Why is it so hard?
No...don't look!
(For Yiu Wai-lan and Yau You-fong's safety)
(and all goes well. From : Man Nga-kei)
Man Nga-kei, you're still thinking of
that scumbag?
We used to be family.
I'm just praying for their safety.
Yau You-fong is safe because of you,
not Heaven.
You risked your life to save him
but he's now with that witch.
He thinks she saved his life.
And you? He didn't even thank you.
He sent his regards at the hospital.
I wasn't hurt.
I didn't tell him I pulled him up.
Why didn't you?
He only has eyes for Sylvia.
If I told him,
someone would think I'm fighting for him.
Even the tree won't bless the scumbag.
How could you still defend him?
Stop calling him a scumbag.
We were divorced when he met Sylvia.
He wasn't a two-timer or a scumbag.
OK...he's not a scumbag. But you're lovesick
and can't let go but act indifferent.
Liz, I know you care about me,
but I really need a bit more time...
Your flat is full of his paintings
and you're still making payments
with him on the flat.
It'll take forever to get over him.
Why don't you sell the flat,
get your money back and cut yourself loose?
No, the property market is in a slump.
I don't want to cut losses right now.
You're driving me crazy.
Yes!
Look, Liz! The tree changed its mind.
Are you done? Can we go now?
(Man Nga-kei)
Chris, has it been ten years since
we last saw each other?
Probably.
You were quite earnest in high school.
I thought you were a bookworm.
But now, you're tall and handsome
just like an oppa. Right, Angie?
Angie, Liz said you're a copywriter
at a TV station
and you know just about everything.
I'd like to talk to you more.
I only did the research when
I had a show to do.
I only know a little bit...
I heard you're quite a gourmet,
let's order some food.
Angie, what would you like?
Whatever. I'll let you decide.
Mom, happy birthday.
Here's to your good health.
Most importantly, to your beauty.
Good boy!
Sylvia and I bought you a present.
Auntie, happy birthday.
Open it and take a look.
Thank you.
It's beautiful.
I know nothing about jade.
Sylvia picked it out.
Here. I'll put it on for you.
Great!
You did a show on local ruins?
I like to watch urban exploration
when I was abroad.
Anything special about the local ruins?
It's much easier to find them in Hong Kong.
Because in the US or Europe...
Auntie!
Angie!
Happy birthday, here's to your good health.
Thank you...
Cantonese opera classics?
How did you manage to find them?
I hope you like them.
A colleague in the music department
was selling them.
Then they must be expensive.
You're so sweet,
but your memory is getting worse.
No, I saw you having dinner with
Davis and his girlfriend last night
in a restaurant.
I just didn't want to intrude.
You were there?
Dinner was unbearable.
Why did you start playing the stock market?
Sylvia taught you?
Auntie, are you interested?
I can get you some information.
No need. My son and I don't have
any luck with making quick money.
Nothing can help our luck.
Whether one knows how to invest,
cannot be summed up by just saying
you don't have luck with quick money.
After my son met this witch,
he's definitely out of luck.
Thanks.
The Boss wants to know what you're doing.
Did you finish the sketch?
Where are you?
Call him back.
Last time, you didn't show up
and the client was pissed.
I'm not surprised he doesn't like
your design.
In our business, the client must come first.
If you don't understand, you should quit.
If you wish to invest in real estate,
I think you should pick the East.
I drew the Three of Wands.
Is my destiny overseas?
It favors overseas development.
Investing in real estate in SE Asia
is the right thing to do.
Why SE Asia? What does it stand for?
That doesn't matter.
Investment is about ROI, rate of return.
Rent in SE Asia is about 4% to 6%,
which is higher than Hong Kong.
You're an investor too?
Of course. Why would I miss out
on a good thing?
Is overseas investment suitable for me?
Yes,
but I thought you're not
interested in investments.
I thought it's just a game for you.
I used to think it was great I can
make money doing something I like.
Now I prefer to make money.
If the clients don't appreciate my work,
why waste my time and effort on them?
Why? More changes on your design?
Not to mention the games
the Boss is playing.
I did everything the client wanted
and changed the design.
But the Boss kept saying the client
still didn't like it
and wanted me to start from scratch.
He obviously wanted me to quit.
Don't be mad.
You're angry because I gave you the idea.
They don't appreciate a good idea.
I didn't realize I mean so much to you.
I should have followed your lead to invest.
Then I don't need to work for anyone
and take crap from them.
Every decision has a cause and effect.
If you were not in design,
you wouldn't have taken on the
renovation of S Bar.
If you never went to S Bar,
we wouldn't have met.
Now that we have met,
should I follow your lead to invest?
Whether you invest your money in
real estate or your love in me,
there are risks involved.
Sometimes, you need guts to make money.
Some people are more suitable
to work for someone else.
There. I exposed you as a quack.
It's in your fate.
But it still depends on if you have
the smarts for it
and how you go by doing it.
I have done a lot of homework.
It's not a random decision.
How hard is the homework?
You better start doing it.
Wait up!
I might have goaded you a bit,
there's no need to stay up all night.
I couldn't stop reading.
I have an initial idea already.
Take a look at these buildings.
Thailand?
The ROI on these areas is high.
But they're quite expensive, my budget...
we can go in on it.
I considered more than the ROI,
but also which areas are suitable for us.
These building should be OK for both of us.
When we went camping and mentioned
overseas properties,
you sounded like you yearn for it.
I guess you want to invest in
overseas property
because you want to live there.
Yes, I do...
Like me, you don't want to be tied down.
I'm not trying to trap you with a flat.
For such a huge investment,
I can only chip in a small share.
That's easy. I'll pay for the big share.
If we can sort out the money,
this is a good plan.
I didn't like to plan ahead,
but meeting you gave me more possibilities.
Such as?
Such as...getting married and have kids.
What about getting married but no kids?
Or have kids without getting married.
Either way...nothing has to change.
As long as we're happy, just like right now.
I don't think my fate is right
for this area.
Well...I'll do what I do best.
I'll go change and get you breakfast.
See you at 8:30 p.m. next Monday,
on Overseas Property Guide.
You know anything about overseas property?
You seem quite interested.
Anyone with extra money would check out
overseas property.
It's not as expensive as Hong Kong
and the ROI is much higher.
Just like Thailand, in Bangkok alone,
the ROI is around 5% to 6%.
Phuket is even higher at 8%.
What does that mean? You pay the downpayment
someone else will pay the mortgage for you.
You seem to know a lot.
Are you so confident?
80% if not 100%.
I looked up everything in Thailand.
You spent a lot of money on downpayment.
Then invested in something else.
Do you still have money left?
I'm short on my own.
But you have.
Mom, let's make an investment
and make some money together.
Count me out.
I know nothing about overseas property.
It's too risky.
Besides, all my money is in time deposit.
If I withdraw now, there'll be a penalty.
No thanks.
Mom, you're doing your Maths wrong.
If the interest rate of the time deposit
cannot keep up with inflation,
you're actually losing money.
Owning property is different.
Rent will go up with inflation,
you can't lose.
Sylvia and I will chip in the money.
She already has a broker in Thailand.
What? You're partnering with the witch?
Don't listen to her.
Mom, stop calling her a witch.
I read through the information myself.
I formed my own judgment.
How long have you known her?
She's asking you for money already?
Last time I told her we don't have
much luck with making quick money.
She already contradicted me.
Come to think of it,
she already planned to ask you
for money back then.
Don't fall for it, son!
You don't like her because
she contradicted you.
I have the freedom to choose.
You can't stop me from seeing anyone.
Forget it. I'll be in my room.
Look at you. You were not like this before.
You yelled at me because of a witch?
I just don't want anyone to swindle you.
Angie!
What's up? What's so urgent?
I need to discuss something with you.
Let's sell the flat and split the money.
All of a sudden?
We agreed I can stay there
and pay you rent.
Yes, it's my fault. I need money.
Or we can keep the flat,
you pay me back for the downpayment
and I'll surrender the title.
Wait! What's the rush?
I saw a few properties in Thailand.
They're cheap and the ROI is much higher
than Hong Kong.
I don't want to miss the opportunity.
I'm chipping in with my girlfriend Sylvia.
She already contacted a real estate agent,
I don't want to hold her off.
That's why I need the money.
OK, but you have never invested in anything.
Did something happen at work?
You're not happy?
My interest is in design.
But I must compromise to make a living.
I just want to make my first pot of gold
while I'm still young.
There's no room for ideals unless
you have money.
I can't miss this opportunity.
That makes sense.
But why the sudden decision?
Which corporation is responsible for
the project?
Can it be trusted?
Do you know anything about it?
I have done my homework.
I studied Bangkok and Phuket
and did all the calculations.
Bangkok is a major city,
the flat will be rented out to locals.
Phuket is different.
It's mainly rented out to tourists.
Look at the ROI,
it's really high and worth investing.
Are you kidding me?
What's wrong with you?
Do you really want to buy property?
You wrote in your sketch book!
This is your life's work.
This is where you put down your ideas.
You're not the Yau You-fong I know.
He's not impulsive.
You didn't even go out there
and you talk about owning property?
What's wrong with you?
You're a designer, remember?
You told me a client's content
is a designer's greatest satisfaction.
Because design is not an interest or a hobby
it's a pursuit of ideals.
You didn't even go out there!
But you want to buy a flat
based on a leaflet?
OK, you want to buy a flat?
You want money?
You can have the flat back.
Go buy your new flat.
I can't figure this out. Can you help me?
Sure!
You're not the Yau You-fong I know.
He's not impulsive.
I signed the power of attorney.
The law firm will send it to you.
This is your net worth.
Decide for yourself if this is
how you want to invest.
Try putting your hand behind you.
Raise your head a little.
Done. It's perfect.
Really?
You look so handsome.
Let me see...
You made me look fat.
Your painting skill failed.
That's because you're a poor teacher.
But you'll have more time to teach me
from now on.
Sylvia, about buying overseas property.
I think we should think twice...
True. I spoke to the real estate agent.
He said the cost-performance ratio
is rather high for these buildings,
He bought one for himself.
I already confirmed with him verbally.
You did?
Yes, weren't you very keen?
Yes, but we haven't actually seen it.
People are fighting for quality property
like this.
Act on it once you made up your mind
or it'll be gone.
Still. We should think it over.
Let's not rush into it.
Are you toying with me?
When I was thinking, you said it was OK.
Now that I spoke to the agent,
you want to go back on your word.
I'm sorry, I was too impulsive.
It's better to calm down.
We should spend more time to understand
the overseas market
to minimize our risks.
You know I'm not good with
long-term investments.
Besides, money is an issue.
I don't have enough money for you.
Look, I'm not asking you to give me money,
we're both chipping in.
But I don't have enough.
I can't ask Mom for money
and make her bear the risk.
I also promised to give the flat to my ex.
I can't go back on my word.
I see. Your mother and ex don't want us
to invest or be together.
No, they're against making the investment.
Why do you need your ex's approval?
What kind of ex is she?
There's nothing between us.
Nothing?
You changed your tune after talking to her.
Does that mean you listen to her
and she's more important? Then what am I?
Nothing I say matters, right?
Come on, listen to me...
Don't touch me! Go back to your ex!
Sylvia!
Calm down and let me explain.
What's there to explain?
I met with my ex to discuss
selling our flat.
Are you selling?
No, right?
That means you're not over her
and you want to dump me for her.
You talked about our future
and how we invest together
and move overseas.
That's just talk.
You have not thought about our future.
No, Sylvia!
Precisely because I'm thinking about
our future, we must be careful
and not put all our eggs in one basket.
I don't want any accidents.
What accidents?
You think I'm swindling your money?
That's not what I mean.
Then what do you mean?
You had no intention to sell
your flat, right?
Don't bother. Get out!
Are you OK?
Let me dress your wound.
Don't bother!
You're a hypocrite! You're lying.
No, I'm not. I do love you, Sylvia.
Then sell your flat.
No?
Why can't you give me more time to think?
Because I think you're lying.
All along, you're still in love with her.
I have nothing to say to you. Get out!
Sylvia...
Out!
Calm down! I'll call you.
(several days later)
We'll talk when you get over this.
Are you feeling better?
Let's go for dessert buffet.
(Sylvia on live)
Hello, everyone! I'm in a good mood today.
20% off on all orgonite pyramids
and crystal bracelets.
She's in the mood to livestream
but not in the mood to call me?
Want some fruits?
Amethyst can clear your head...
What are you watching?
Sylvia's livestreaming.
Leave a message if you want them.
This quack's crystals are trash.
Exactly! Wearing it is worse than before.
She claims they're consecrated.
That's the excuse to jack up the price.
She's treating us like suckers.
The effect of crystals depends on the user.
If you don't have the right vibe,
the crystal cannot raise the dead.
Where did these anti-fans come from?
What are anti-fans?
People who maliciously criticize someone.
Don't bother to defend yourself,
you bloody hag!
She's neither Chinese nor western,
neither fish nor fowl.
She's nothing but a quack!
She used black magic to steal a guy
from a client.
Is that true? That's malicious!
You're free to say anything
just make sure you have proof.
Look! Someone just spilled the beans
and posted a link.
See for yourselves.
What are all those contraptions?
Those are fakes. It's not true.
Don't believe any of it.
Is she after you?
Of course not! Sylvia is not like that.
It's hard to say, she's a witch!
She's capable of anything.
When you pulled out of the investment,
she turned against you right away.
She's just jealous.
She thought I'm not yet over Angie.
I handled the situation poorly.
No wonder she's angry with me.
You may know her face, but not her heart.
Why else would so many people
point out her problems?
Sylvia is obviously under
intentional attack.
Why would there be so many anti-fans
and they are very organized.
The damaging information does not
need any substantiation.
Angie!
Auntie!
Here's the power of attorney.
Thank you, Auntie.
Thank goodness for you,
or else that witch would have
swindled the flat.
Davis should know what he's doing.
Maybe he's under pressure at work
and he got mixed up.
Don't be mad at him. He loves you.
Only you can make him come to his senses.
How are things with Sylvia?
They probably broke up.
That witch was openly criticized online.
Davis finally saw her for who she was.
It seems to have turned into a big deal.
I have heard about it too.
I didn't realize she would con money
and use black magic.
She's not to be trifled with.
I checked and found out
she tied Davis' birth data to a gourd.
A gourd is supposed to gather wealth.
She acted so sweet before.
When Davis refused to invest with her,
she turned hostile right away
and went crazy.
But that brat is still not convinced.
He planned to talk to her after work.
I hope he'll wake up.
I took her on before,
I knew she's not that simple.
Auntie, you took her on? How?
That time when we first met.
Angie, you're so sweet.
You're willing to give up the flat
for my son.
Honestly, even I can't do something
so noble.
Auntie, it doesn't matter now.
As long as everything turned out OK.
You asked me to get fertilizer and
sphagnum moss for you.
I bought that and also black diamond soil.
That's useful. Take them home later.
Angie, you're so thoughtful.
It's been a week. Don't be mad anymore.
Let's sit down and talk.
I'm on my way over to your studio.
Let's talk about this.
Sylvia, open the door, OK?
Let's sit down and talk.
Sylvia?
Scumbag, I don't want to see you anymore.
I will not forgive you.
I'm returning your things.
What you owe me, I won't let it slide.
You're still thinking about her.
What do you mean?
It's not what you think, Sylvia!
What's wrong, Mom?
What's going on?
Why so many moths?
It's a bad omen.
Just kidding. Come on...
It's about to rain.
Don't mind them. They'll go away later.
Why did you yell?
To wake you up.
What? You're scared of moths?
I'm afraid you're scared of them.
(private number)
Sylvia, is that you?
Just talk to me.
It's no use playing with the phone.
Mr. Yau, we have a problem with the flat.
This is outrageous!
Look what happened!
You told me to clean up the place,
this is what I saw when I opened the door.
It's OK. You may go. I'll handle this.
OK.
Did you do this? What do you want?
Where are you? Let's meet and talk, OK?
Sylvia?
I told you I'll make you sorry.
Calm down. Take it easy!
Angie?!
(Chan Sin To Memorial Primary School)
Angie, where are you?
Sylvia, answer me!
Angie!
Angie...Angie, wake up...
Davis...
Don't move...
I'll get you out.
Be careful!
Don't worry!
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
Does it hurt anywhere else?
Who brought you here?
I was late getting off work.
On my way home,
I was walking and someone
covered up my face
and I passed out.
Did you see who it was?
No, I didn't.
But I've been harassed lately.
(Leave someone else's boyfriend alone,
bloody whore!)
(If you don't let go, I will take action.)
I think it was Sylvia.
I got you into this mess.
Why did you stop?
Go up and let me dress your wound.
No, I don't want to scare Auntie.
Just take me home.
OK, I'll take you home.
I'll walk you up.
Think nothing of it.
Yau You-fong!